const week2Data = [
   {
      question: "In the context of Industry 4.0, what is the full form of CPS?",
      options: [
        "Controlled Power System",
        "Customer Provisioning Service",
        "Cloud Processing Service",
        "Cyber Physical Systems",
      ],
      answer: "Cyber Physical Systems",
    },
    {
      question:
        "State True or False. Business, providing information goods, has virtually zero transportation and replication cost.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      answer: "True",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following technologies is used by research scientists to selectively modify the DNA of living organisms?",
      options: [
        "3D Printing",
        "Nanomedicine",
        "Liquid Biopsy",
        "Genetic Engineering",
      ],
      answer: "Genetic Engineering",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following statements is true about addressing an economic crisis or recession?",
      options: [
        "Observing an increase in prices of major commodities is a key indicator.",
        "Increasing productivity and reducing costs can help recover from a recession.",
        "The main economy of manufacturing location should always be based on only one resource to avoid crisis.",
        "Recovery from a depression is faster than recovery from a recession when the same solution is applied.",
      ],
      answer:
        "Increasing productivity and reducing costs can help recover from a recession.",
    },
    {
      question: "What does ERP stand for in the context of ICT?",
      options: [
        "Enterprise Resource Planning",
        "Electronic Resource Platform",
        "Enhanced Reporting Protocol",
        "Economic Resource Planning",
      ],
      answer: "Enterprise Resource Planning",
    },
    {
      question:
        "How can enterprises improve sustainability with respect to energy consumption?",
      options: [
        "Increasing usage on non-renewable energy sources",
        "Reducing energy consumption from non-renewable sources and increasing use of renewable energy",
        "Focusing solely on reducing renewable energy costs",
        "Ignoring energy price fluctuations",
      ],
      answer:
        "Reducing energy consumption from non-renewable sources and increasing use of renewable energy",
    },
    {
      question:
        "What is the primary goal of 'Just-In-Time' in a Lean Production System?",
      options: [
        "Ensuring each process produces what is needed by the next process in a continuous flow",
        "Producing in advance to meet potential future demand",
        "Reducing production costs by purchasing cheap materials",
        "Increasing inventory to minimize disruptions",
      ],
      answer:
        "Ensuring each process produces what is needed by the next process in a continuous flow",
    },
    {
      question: "What is a 'value stream' in a Lean Production System?",
      options: [
        "A set of tools for production",
        "All the actions required for a product from order to delivery",
        "A method of employee training",
        "A type of waste reduction",
      ],
      answer: "All the actions required for a product from order to delivery",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is an objective of Lean Production in Industry 4.0?",
      options: [
        "Increasing waste in processes to improve flexibility",
        "Focusing on non-value-added activities to reduce costs",
        "Identifying waste in processes and eliminating it",
        "Eliminating continuous improvement efforts",
      ],
      answer: "Identifying waste in processes and eliminating it",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following technologies is a medium for achieving smart and connected systems?",
      options: [
        "Embedded Systems",
        "Traditional Mechanical Systems",
        "Manual Control Systems",
        "Non-Interactive Devices",
      ],
      answer: "Embedded Systems",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following are key attributes of a smart business model?",
      options: [
        "Manual processes, cost reduction, and labor dependency",
        "Value proposition, revenue streams, and technologies",
        "Traditional marketing, fixed costs, and limited innovation",
        "Centralized control, non-digital strategies, and fixed processes",
      ],
      answer: "Value proposition, revenue streams, and technologies",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not a component of a Smart Factory?",
      options: [
        "Smart machines",
        "Smart manufacturing processes",
        "Information Technology",
        "Physical ledgers",
      ],
      answer: "Physical ledgers",
    },
    {
      question:
        "In the Automation Pyramid of a Smart Factory, which level is just above the Device Level?",
      options: [
        "Control Level",
        "ERP Level",
        "Manufacturing execution system level",
        "None of these",
      ],
      answer: "Control Level",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a prerequisite of the Industrial Internet of Things?",
      options: [
        "Security",
        "Incompatibility",
        "Interoperability",
        "Scalability",
      ],
      answer: "Incompatibility",
    },
    {
      question:
        "In which format is healthcare data transmitted to maintain data uniformity and interoperability?",
      options: ["HL-7", "LH-5", "HD-7", "None of these"],
      answer: "HL-7",
    },
  ],
